Guide to the Nate Brown Western Sound Archive Collection ARS.0124
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 2546. Glenn Gould Recital, Salzburg 8/25/59; Karajan, Berlin Philharmonic, Gould 1957, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2553. Holland Festival Transcriptions, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2554. Josef Hofmann, Piano. 11/28/37 [IPL 5001/2]; 4/7/38 [IPL 5007/8], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2559. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2560. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2561. Silvestri, Philadelphia Orchestra 11/61; Munch, Philadelphia Orchestra 3/1963, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)